{
    "subject": "resource/Ghost_Chasers",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of Ghost Chasers is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9599224925041199,
            "question": "Is English the primary language used by Ghost Chasers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9409511685371399,
            "question": "Why is English considered the language of Ghost Chasers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.884145975112915,
            "question": "Are there any other languages spoken by Ghost Chasers besides English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8701586723327637,
            "question": "Can Ghost Chasers communicate in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8621601462364197,
            "question": "Are there any linguistic challenges faced by Ghost Chasers when using English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8553077578544617,
            "question": "How does the English language contribute to the effectiveness of Ghost Chasers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8477371335029602,
            "question": "What language do Ghost Chasers speak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8170944452285767,
            "question": "What are some common phrases used by Ghost Chasers in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.81292325258255,
            "question": "Is the use of English important for the work of Ghost Chasers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7732313275337219,
            "question": "Do all Ghost Chasers speak English fluently?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Ghost Chasers is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6580_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the use of English important for the work of Ghost Chasers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6580_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common phrases used by Ghost Chasers in English?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6580_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language do Ghost Chasers speak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6580_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6580_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents do support the statement that \"The language of Ghost Chasers is English.\" This can be inferred from several pieces of information provided, such as the pronunciation given in British and U.S. English, the etymology mentioned (formed within English), and the use of English words and phrases throughout the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}